/*
   lundi 21 mars 202209:28:51
   User: 
   Server: DESKTOP-1FNA1GH
   Database: AUTOPC
   Application: 
*/

'Utilisateurs' table
- Unable to create index 'PK_Utilisateurs'.  
The CREATE UNIQUE INDEX statement terminated because a duplicate key was found for the object name 'dbo.Utilisateurs' and the index name 'PK_Utilisateurs'. The duplicate key value is ().
Could not create constraint or index. See previous errors.
The statement has been terminated.

